BANANI NAG

OBJECTIVE

Highly Motivated Individual and a diligent operations associate with experience of maintaining seamless business operation as well as customer service and sales operations, being a fast learner capable to cope up with new ambience and work areas.

EXPERIENCE

• ICICI Bank

05/2022 - 08/2022

Deputy Manager -DSMG Working as a Collection Manager for NPA customers of HL,PL,CV,Auto Loans

Incedo Inc.

12/2021 - 05/2022

Associate

Investment Banking Operations

HSBC

01/2020 - 12/2021

Special Project

Responsible for Corporate action of Singapore. Training new joiner and act as a checker. Direct reports to onshore.

Etravels

(10/2014 - 12/2019)

Sales Manager

EDUCATION

West Bengal Council of Higher Secondary Education

2011

Higher Secondary/12th 71%

University of Calcutta

2014

B.Com 43

Vidyasagar University

2016

M.Com 42

Pondicherry University

2017-2019

MBA Finance Drop-out CONTACT

@ iambananinag@gmail.com

9163811107

AC215/B Prafullakanan(E) Kestopur Kolkata 700101

SKILLS

Customer support, sales, Banking collection, Banking operations

Bills Payable, Invoices.

LANGUAGES

English

Bengali (Native)

Hindi

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth : 25/08/1993

Marital Status: Married

Indian Institute of Management, Kozhikode

2022-2023

Certificate on HR Management and Analytics 90